# **WONG SAU XUAN**

wongsx-pm21@student.tarc.edu.my
23, Lorong Panchor Indah 13,
Tama PPanchor Indah,
14300, Nibong Tebal

010-3420893

August 23, 2022

Sophic Automation Sdn Bhd 6 & 8, Lorong Perindustrian Bukit Minyak 1/1, Kawasan Perindustrian Bukit Minyak, 14100 Simpang Ampat, Penang, Malaysia.

Dear Mr/Ms,

I am Wong Sau Xuan. I would like to apply for a ten-week Internship Program (14-Nov-2022 to 22-Jan-2023) at your company in the field of computer science. This program is an experiential learning opportunity where I can enhance my skills and gain practical work experience before getting into a proper job.

For your information, I am currently pursuing a Diploma in Computer Science at Tunku Abdul Rahman University College, Penang Branch Campus. I am in the first semester of my second year, and my current CGPA is 3.6875. I graduated high school in 2020 at SMK Tunku Abdul Rahman, Nibong Tebal. As my academic records show, I am skilled in several programming languages such as C language, Java, SQL, JavaScript, and HTML. I am good at communication skills and am fluent in Mandarin, Malay, English and Hokkien. During my leisure time, I enjoy learning and keeping up with the current trends and technologies.

I am keen to develop my professional skills and look forward to discussing my application with you at an interview. I have enclosed a copy of my resume for your consideration. I would be available for an interview anytime. Please feel free to contact me via phone at 010-3420893 or email (wongsx-pm21@student.tarc.edu.my).

Wong Sau Xuan



# **WONG SAU XUAN**

- **1** 010-3420893
- wongsx-pm21@student.tarc.edu.my
- 23, Lorong Panchor Indah 13, Taman Panchor Indah, 14300 Nobong Tebal, Pulau Pinang

Α

# **EDUCATION**

#### SECONDARY SCHOOL

SMK Tunku Abdul Rahman

Jan 2016 - Dec 2020

### SIJIL PELAJARAN MALAYSIA

- Malay B+ Science
- English D Additional Mathematics C+
- Moral B+ Account A+
- History A Economics B
- Mathematics A Chinese B+

### **DIPLOMA IN COMPUTER SCIENCE**

Tunku Abdul Rahman University College (TAR UC) Penang Branch Campus

Jun 2021 - Present

• Current Cumulative Grade Point Average(CGPA): 3.6875

### **EXPERIENCE**

#### HIN LIM FURNITURE MANUFACTURER SDN. BHD

Position: Stock Management & Operator

May 2021 - Jun 2021 (Part Time)

- record and check the stock status and balance
- communicate with other operator and manager

#### **YS Foam Industries**

Position: Operator

May 2022 - Jun 2022 (Part Time)

- Communicate with other operator and manager
- Teamwork with others

# **SKILLS**

- C Language - JavaScript

- HTML - Java

- CSS - SQL

# **LANGUAGE**

	Writing	Speaking
MANDARIN	Excellent	Excellent
ENGLISH	Good	Good
MALAY	Good	Good

## **VOLUNTER EXPERIENCE**

- An active member and committee member of School Volleyball Team at SMK Tunku Abdul Rahman
- Treasurer of Scout at SMK Tunku Abdul Rahman

### **REFERENCE**

1. Name: Mr. Choo Yun Bei

Relation: Lecturer and student

Contact no.: 0165996305

2.Name: Liew Pui Fong

Relation: Lecturer and student

Contact.no: 04 - 899 5230 ext 215